Guide to the Yale Law School Faculty, Governing Board, and Board of Permanent Officers Meeting Minutes
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Law School, faculty, governing board, and board of permanent officers meeting minutes
1883-1981
RU 450
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(3 boxes)
The materials consist of minutes of meetings documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Law School faculty, governing board, and Board of Permanent Officers.
Yale Law School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26-C (YRG 26-C), Records of officers and faculty of the Yale Law School. The original minutes for 1950-1981 on reels 3 and 4 are held by the Yale Law School.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Conditions Governing Access
The entire collection has been microfilmed. Patrons must use HM 130 instead of the originals.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of minutes of meetings documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Law School faculty, governing board, and Board of Permanent Officers.
Law schools; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Faculty
- Minutes of the faculty, governing board, and Board of Permanent Officers, 1883-1981; Accession 1981-A-017
  Conditions Governing Access
  Reel 1 and reel 2 open for research; reel 3 is restricted until January 1, 2057.
  - Volume 1
    - Faculty, 1883 January 12 - 1893 September 16 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
    - Governing Board, 1892 March 10 - 1902 September 6 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
  - Volume 2
    - Faculty, 1883 January 12 - 1893 September 16 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
  - Volume 3
    - Faculty, 1892 March 10 - 1904 December 21 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
  - Volume 4
    - Governing Board, 1902 November 3- 1916 March 25 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
  - Volume 5
    - Faculty, 1917 October 9 - 1922 December 20 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Governing Board, 1918 November 5 - 1921 December 8 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
  - Volume 6
    - Faculty, 1923 January 10 - 1929 December 12 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Governing Board, 1923 May 9 - 1928 January 24 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1928 February 4 - 1929 May 21 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
  - Volume 7
    - Faculty, 1930 January 9 - 1933 June 15 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1930 February 27 - 1933 June 8 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
  - Volume 8
    - Faculty, 1933 September 23 - 1936 December 17 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1934 February 26 - 1936 November 18 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
  - Volume 9
    - Faculty, 1937 January 7 - 1940 December 19 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1937 April 29 - 1940 June 4 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
  - Volume 10
    - Faculty, 1941 January 16 - 1949 December 8 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Governing Board, 1946 April 24, 1947 January 16 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1941 February 17 - 1949 December 13 (Box 2, Reel 2U)
  - Restricted records
    These records are restricted until January 1, 2057.
    - Volume 11
      - Faculty, 1950 January 5 - 1954 June 2 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
      - Board of Permanent Officers, 1950 February 21 - 1954 May 4 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 12
      - Faculty, 1954 September 23 - 1957 June 6 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
      - Board of Permanent Officers, 1956 May 22 - August 17 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 13
      - Faculty, 1957 May 30 - 1960 June 9 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 14
      - Faculty, 1960 September 22 - 1965 June 8 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 15
      - Faculty, 1965 oct 7 - 1970 June 2 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 16
      - Faculty, 1970 September 17 - 1975 May 15 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 17
      - Faculty, 1975 September 19 - 1981 June 9 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 18
      - Governing Board, 1956 March 30 - 1960 May 19 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
      - Board of Permanent Officers, 1954 December 16 - 1956 May 7 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 19
      - Governing Board, 1960 November 23 - 1965 June 8 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 20
      - Governing Board, 1965 October 28 - 1970 May 13 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 21
      - Governing Board, 1970 September 30 - 1975 May 20 (Box 3, Reel 3U)
    - Volume 22
      - Governing Board, 1975 October 29 - 1981 October 5 (Box 3, Reel 3U)